Hi, my name is Andrew Trask, and I'm a PhD
大家好 我是 Andrew Trask
student at the University of Oxford,
我是牛津大学的博士生
studying deep learning for natural
在研究深度学习中的
language processing. Deep learning, as I'm
自然语言处理
sure you are coming to understand, is a suite of
大家所要学的深度学习
tools that allows you to take what you
就是一套工具 让我们根据已知的数据
know, and predict what you want to know
通过使用神经网络
using neural networks. Natural language
预测我们想要知道的事物
processing is the study of human
自然语言处理就是对人类语言的研究
language using tools such as machine
使用一系列工具 如机器学习
learning, and in this case, deep learning.
在我们的课程中 也就是深度学习
In this tutorial, we're going to be
本课程中 我们将学习
talking about sentiment classification,
情感分类
or the classification of whether or not
这种分类能够
a section of human generated text is
判断人类生成的一段文字
positive or negative. So in this case,
是正面或是负面的 所以 在此情况下
what we know is a section of human
我们已知一段人类生成的语言文本
generated text, and we want to know is
想要预测的是
one of these positive or negative labels.
这些正面或负面标签之一
Now, what this tutorial is really going
本课程真正要做的
to be about, is about framing a problem,
就是解构问题
so the network can be successful in
这样 我们的神经网络才能
discovering correlation between your
成功发现
input and your output data. Sentiment
输入和输出数据之间的相关性
classification is really good for this,
情感分类非常适合做这件事
because neural nets don't naturally accept
因为神经网络不能直接接受
texts input, they accept numbers. So what we're
文本输入 它只接受数字输入
going to have to do, is transform our
所以 我们要做的
textual input data into numerical form
就是将文本输入数据转换成数字形式
in such a way that the neural network can
以一种神经网络可以
easily discover the correlation. Our
轻易找到相关性的方式来呈现
goal is going to be to be able to see
我们的目标就是
how can we change the way that we do
看看我们如何改变方式来完成
this that we set our problem in such a
如何构造我们的问题
way that the neural net discovers
可以让神经元能够
correlation as quickly and easily as
快速轻易地找到相关性
Now, what I'm going to assume you already
现在 我假设大家已经
know is basically what you learned so
具备了一些基础知识
far in Udacity course. So neural networks, forward and
上过优达学城的课程 包括神经网络
back propagation, stochastic gradient descent,
正向和反向传播 梯度下降
mean square error, and train/test split
平均方差 和训练集/测试集划分
that all shall be quite familiar to you at
这些你都应该相当熟悉了
this point. If you become
如果你觉得有些不熟
unfamiliar, feel unprepared for any
觉得准备不充分
of these prerequisites, I  encourage
我鼓励大家
you first to go back and check out the
回去看看之前几周的课程
weeks, and if you would prefer to hear it
如果你想换一种方式学
in another way, or perhaps the textual away,
可能是书面的方式
you can also check out your companion
你可以看看我的书
guide, Grokking Deep Learning, which is a
Grokking Deep Learning
book that I write. My publisher - Manning
这本书是我写的 我的出版商万宁公司
publications is generous enough to
非常慷慨
offer forty percent discount code to all
为所有优达学城的学员
Udacity students. I'm also been
提供了六折的优惠码
hanging out on the slack channel for you
我也会在 Slack 频道上与你们互动
to ask questions along the way.
回答问题
So, this tutorial is going to be broken
本教程将由
into six different projects,
六个项目组成
the first one is going to start with
第一个项目
curating your dataset, and kind of
你将整理数据
coming up with a predictive theory for
并构想出一个预测理论
where we think the correlation exists in
考虑数据中的相关性究竟是如何的
our dataset. And then we're going to
接下来
validate this theory,
我们将验证这一理论
we're going to... Once we validate the theory,
当验证完理论
we're going to transform it into your
我们将理论运用到输入和输出数据中
to iterate several times, and try to
然后重复迭代几次
increase the amount of correlation that
训练神经网络 使它能够尽可能
our neural networks are able to find in a
在更短的时间内找到更高的相关性
we're actually going to tear apart our
最后 我们会把神经网络解构拆分开来
neural networks and check out the weights
研究其中的权重系数矩阵
to really understand what's going on when
真正理解我们的反向传播过程
we're back-propagating, to try to solve assignment
尝试完成我们布置的有关神经网络中权重系数的作业
further ado, let's get started.
废话少说 就让我们开始吧